in this exercise
we are asked to create an empty string
using the string class and assign it to
a variable
so let's call our variable empty string
and one way that we can create an empty
string
is to call the new method
on the string class new is a class
method
when we call new on the string class
with no arguments passed in
like you see on line 1 an empty string
is returned
and in this case we are assigning that
empty string
to the local variable empty string
and let's output the value of empty
string
using the p method to see that
[Music]
when we run our code you can see that
we've output an empty string
now there's one other way that we could
create an empty string here
and that's using a string literal so
let's
comment out our code on line one
and this time we'll assign the local
variable empty string
to just an empty string
again let's run our code in output empty
string
so there are two ways that we can create
an empty string
either with a string literal or by
calling the
new method on the string class